question_data = [
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "American rapper Dr. Dre actually has a Ph.D. doctorate.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "Scatman John&#039;s real name was John Paul Larkin.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "Eurobeat is primarily an Italian genre of music.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "In 1993, Prince changed his name to an unpronounceable symbol because he was unhappy with his contract with Warner Bros.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "Stevie Wonder&#039;s real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "A Saxophone is a brass instrument.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "The 2011 movie &quot;The Adventures of Tintin&quot; was directed by Steven Spielberg.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "Daft Punk originated in France.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "Lead Singer Rivers Cuomo of American rock band Weezer attended Harvard.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "Michael Jackson wrote The Simpsons song &quot;Do the Bartman&quot;.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    }
]
